[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "This Fantastic Quiz and Website was created by the extremely humble",
        "category": "General",
        "options": [
            "AbusiveTuna",
            "The Overseer",
            "The Overseer",
            "The Overseer"
        ],
        "answer": "AbusiveTuna"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "This quest gives you the ability to use Fairy Rings",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Fairytale II - Cure a Queen",
            "Fairytale I - Growing Pains",
            "Lost City",
            "Rag and Bone Man I"
        ],
        "answer": "Fairytale II - Cure a Queen"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "A Rat, commonly found throughout Gielinor in sewers, dungeons, etc. Has a combat level of",
        "category": "General",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "3",
            "10",
            "128"
        ],
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Burying regular bones grants the player __ Prayer xp",
        "category": "General",
        "options": [
            "4.5",
            "5",
            "9",
            "10"
        ],
        "answer": "4.5"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Created as a training ground by the Amlodd Clan to ensure their warrors were capable of defending Prifddinas during the godwars",
        "category": "Lore",
        "options": [
            "The Gauntlet",
            "Fortis Colosseum",
            "The Song of the Elves",
            "Windertodt"
        ],
        "answer": "The Gauntlet"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Before his release, TzTok-Jad's working title was",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Lord Magmus",
            "Jad",
            "TzKal-Jad",
            "TzTok-Zuk"
        ],
        "answer": "Lord Magmus"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Released on October 4th, 2005. This minigame would introduce the first serious PvM challenge to runescape players",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "TzHaar Fight Cave",
            "The Kalphite Queen",
            "The King Black Dragon",
            "Corporeal Beast"
        ],
        "answer": "TzHaar Fight Cave"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Released on June 1st, 2017. This minigame would prove to be the most difficult PvM challenge in osrs for years to come",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "The Inferno",
            "The Chambers of Xeric",
            "Theatre Of Blood",
            "Fortis Colosseum"
        ],
        "answer": "The Inferno"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Released on July 25th 2019, its rewards would later be reworked and redefine the Iron game Ranged Meta with its Powerful Bow",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "The Corrupted Gauntlet",
            "Zulrah",
            "The Chambers of Xeric",
            "The Inferno"
        ],
        "answer": "The Corrupted Gauntlet"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "This boss held the title of 'Strongest Monster' for 2113 days",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Verzik Vitur",
            "TzKal-Zuk",
            "Great Olm",
            "TzTok-Jad"
        ],
        "answer": "Verzik Vitur"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "This Mob held the title of 'Strongest Monster' for 32 days",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Black Knight",
            "Moss giant",
            "Ice Giant",
            "Greater Demon"
        ],
        "answer": "Black Knight"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "This player was the first to beat the Inferno",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Woox",
            "Synq",
            "Port Khazard",
            "Gnomonkey"
        ],
        "answer": "Woox"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "This player was the first to beat Sol Heredit",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Port Khazard",
            "Synq",
            "Woox",
            "Gnomonkey"
        ],
        "answer": "Port Khazard"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "This player was the first to kill all four awakend bosses and obtain Blorva",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Synq",
            "Woox",
            "Port Khazard",
            "Gnomonkey"
        ],
        "answer": "Synq"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "The backup of the RuneScape source code that OSRS was created from is dated",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "August 10th 2007",
            "August 25th 2008",
            "December 12th 2007",
            "October 5th 2006"
        ],
        "answer": "August 10th 2007"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Released on August 20th 2003, this quest was the last quest before the release of RS2",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Legends' Quest",
            "Dragon Slayer I",
            "The Grand Tree",
            "Biohazard"
        ],
        "answer": "Legends' Quest"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Released on December 1st 2003, this was the first offical quest of RS2",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Rune Mysteries",
            "Legends' Quest",
            "The Underground Pass",
            "Dragon Slayer I"
        ],
        "answer": "Rune Mysteries"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "This was the 50th quest to be released to runescape",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Legends' Quest",
            "Recipe for Disaster",
            "Dragon Slayer I",
            "A Kingdom Divided"
        ],
        "answer": "Legends' Quest"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "This was the 100th quest to be released to runescape",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "Legends' Quest",
            "Recipe for Disaster",
            "Dragon Slayer II",
            "Monkey Madness"
        ],
        "answer": "Recipe for Disaster"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "This player is known for authoring Rooftop Agility Courses",
        "category": "OSRS History",
        "options": [
            "BigRedJapan",
            "Zezima",
            "Suomi",
            "Lnyx Titan"
        ],
        "answer": "BigRedJapan"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "In the Fight Cave Minigame TzTok-Jad Appears on",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Wave 63",
            "Wave 69",
            "Wave 62",
            "Wave 48"
        ],
        "answer": "Wave 63"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "In the Fight Caves Minigame TzTok-Jad spawns on",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "In the same spot as the Orange Ket-Zek",
            "In the same spot as the Red Ket-Zek",
            "A random tile",
            "In the same spot everytime"
        ],
        "answer": "In the same spot as the Orange Ket-Zek"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "To correctly pray against a Tok-Xil you would use",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Protect From Missiles",
            "Protect From Melee",
            "Protect From Magic",
            "None, its damage is typeless"
        ],
        "answer": "Protect From Missiles"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "To correctly pray against a Ket-Zek you would use",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Protect From Magic",
            "Protect From Missiles",
            "Protect From Melee",
            "None, its damage is typeless"
        ],
        "answer": "Protect From Magic"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "This famous safespot in the Tzhaar Fight Caves is nicknamed after its unique shape",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Italy Rock",
            "West Rock",
            "Claw Rock",
            "Long Rock"
        ],
        "answer": "Italy Rock"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "In the Inferno Zuk Appears on",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Wave 69",
            "Wave 63",
            "Wave 70",
            "Wave 62"
        ],
        "answer": "Wave 69"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "To correctly pray against a Jal-Xil you would use",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Protect From Magic",
            "Protect From Missiles",
            "Protect From Melee",
            "None, its damage is typeless"
        ],
        "answer": "Protect From Missiles"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "To correctly pray against a Jal-Zek you would use",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Protect From Magic",
            "Protect From Missiles",
            "Protect From Melee",
            "None, its damage is typeless"
        ],
        "answer": "Protect from Magic"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "On Wave 68 of the inferno ____ appears ",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Triple Jads",
            "Jad",
            "TzKal-Zuk",
            "Two Jal-Zeks"
        ],
        "answer": "Triple Jads"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "On Wave 67 of the inferno ____ Appears",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Triple Jads",
            "Jad",
            "TzKal-Zuk",
            "Two Jal-Zeks"
        ],
        "answer": "Jad"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "To 'Proc' Healers in the inferno during your fight with TzKal-Zuk you must",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Get him to 240 Hp",
            "Get him to 480 Hp",
            "Kill Jad",
            "Kill the second Mage and Range set"
        ],
        "answer": "Get him to 240 Hp"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "When TzKal-Zuk is below 480 hitpoints",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Jad Spawns",
            "A new Mage/Range set spawns",
            "Healers Spawn",
            "Zuk becomes enraged"
        ],
        "answer": "Jad Spawns"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "Known by many Irons as the 'Red Prison'",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "The Corrupted Gauntlet",
            "Theatre Of Blood",
            "The Chambers of Xeric",
            "The Inferno"
        ],
        "answer": "The Corrupted Gauntlet"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "The item 'Enhanced Crystal Weapon Seed' Has a drop rate of",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "1/400",
            "1/200",
            "1/500",
            "1/300"
        ],
        "answer": "1/400"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Released on June 7th 2018 this PvM encounter is known for its difficulty and loved by the HLC",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "The Inferno",
            "The Chambers of Xeric",
            "Theatre Of Blood",
            "Tombs of Amascut"
        ],
        "answer": "Theatre Of Blood"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "The Theatre of Blood does NOT reward you with which of the following items?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Avernic Defender hilt",
            "Ghrazi Rapier",
            "Scythe of Vitur",
            "Dragon Claws"
        ],
        "answer": "Dragon Claws"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Which of the following armor sets does NOT come from a raid?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Inquisitor",
            "Justiciar",
            "Ancestral",
            "Masori"
        ],
        "answer": "Inquisitor"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "Which of the following armor sets comes from the Theatre of Blood?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Inquisitor",
            "Justiciar",
            "Ancestral",
            "Masori"
        ],
        "answer": "Justiciar"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Which of the following armor sets comes from the Chambers of Xeric?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Virtus",
            "Justiciar",
            "Ancestral",
            "Masori"
        ],
        "answer": "Ancestral"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "The ToA Invocation 'Sprint for It' does what?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Gives players 25 minutes to complete the raid",
            "Gives players 40 minutes to complete the raid",
            "Gives players 15 minutes to complete the raid",
            "Gives players 35 minutes to complete the raid"
        ],
        "answer": "Gives players 25 minutes to complete the raid"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "The ToA Invocation 'Pathmaster' increases the path level by",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "3 levels for every room",
            "2 levels for every room",
            "1 level for every room",
            "1 level randomly throughout the raid"
        ],
        "answer": "3 levels for every room"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "Which of these potions is NOT required to create an Overload?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Elder Potion",
            "Kodai Potion",
            "Twisted Potion",
            "Revitalisation Potion"
        ],
        "answer": "Revitalisation Potion"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "Which of these herbs is NOT found in the Chambers of Xeric?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Golpar",
            "Buchu leaf",
            "Noxifer",
            "Elder cadantine"
        ],
        "answer": "Elder cadantine"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "Which of the following does not boost your combat stats?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Smelling Salts",
            "Overload",
            "Super Combat Potion",
            "Nectar"
        ],
        "answer": "Nectar"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Which of the following Jewels are NOT used for the Keris Partisan",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Breach of the Scarab",
            "Eye of the Corruptor",
            "Jewel of the Sun",
            "Red Topaz"
        ],
        "answer": "Red Topaz"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "The cape 'Icthlarin's shroud (tier 5)' requires what?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "2000 Completions of Tombs of Amascut",
            "2000 Completions of Theatre Of Blood",
            "2000 Completions of Normal Chambers of Xeric",
            "2000 Completions of Challenge Mode Chambers of Xeric"
        ],
        "answer": "2000 Completions of Tombs of Amascut"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "The cape 'Icthlarin's shroud (tier 1)' requires what?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "100 Completions of Tombs of Amascut",
            "500 Completions of Theatre Of Blood",
            "500 Completions of Normal Chambers of Xeric",
            "100 Completions of Challenge Mode Chambers of Xeric"
        ],
        "answer": "100 Completions of Tombs of Amascut"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "Which of the following books is dropped by Ba-Ba?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Apmeken's Capture",
            "Crondis' Capture",
            "Het's Capture",
            "Scabaras' Capture"
        ],
        "answer": "Apmeken's Capture"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "Which of the following books is dropped by Zebak?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Apmeken's Capture",
            "Crondis' Capture",
            "Het's Capture",
            "Scabaras' Capture"
        ],
        "answer": "Crondis' Capture"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "Released on July 25th 2019, this quest follows up the events of Mourning's End Part II",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "The Song of the Elves",
            "Monkey Madness II",
            "Mourning's End Part III",
            "Dragon Slayer II"
        ],
        "answer": "The Song of the Elves"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "Which Quest Boss has the following Quote? \n 'She acted like I was a monster! Come... look upon her monster!'",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Fragment of Seren",
            "Phantom Muspah",
            "Galvek",
            "Bob the Destroyer"
        ],
        "answer": "Fragment of Seren"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "The first offical quest to be created After the release of Old School Runescape",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Monkey Madness II",
            "Dragon Slayer II",
            "King's Ransom",
            "Misthalin Mystery"
        ],
        "answer": "Monkey Madness II"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "Released on May 6th 2016, this quest acted as a continuation of the Gnome Storyline",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Monkey Madness II",
            "Dragon Slayer II",
            "A Kingdom Divided",
            "A night at the Theatre"
        ],
        "answer": "Monkey Madness II"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "This was the last released quest before the source code was archived that would later be used to create OSRS ",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "King's Ransom",
            "Grim Tales",
            "Dream Mentor",
            "Monkey Madness II"
        ],
        "answer": "King's Ransom"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "Released on September 13th 2023, this quest would bring the total number of quest points up to 300",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "The Path of Glouphrie",
            "Desert Treasure II",
            "A Kingdom Divided",
            "Children of the Sun"
        ],
        "answer": "The Path of Glouphrie"
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "Which of these herbs is NOT required for the quest 'Jungle Potion'",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Rogue's purse",
            "Snake weed",
            "Ardrigal",
            "Goutweed"
        ],
        "answer": "Goutweed"
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "This quest sends the adventurer on a journey to slay the dragon Elvarg",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Dragon Slayer II",
            "Dragon Slayer I",
            "Heroes' Quest",
            "Legends' Quest"
        ],
        "answer": "Dragon Slayer I"
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "What is the name of the dragon you must slay in Dragon Slayer I?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Elvarg",
            "The Kendal",
            "Bouncer",
            "Glod"
        ],
        "answer": "Elvarg"
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "Which quest grants you the ability to equip a Rune Platebody",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Dragon Slayer I",
            "Demon Slayer",
            "Waterfall Quest",
            "Shield of Arrav"
        ],
        "answer": "Dragon Slayer I"
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "This quest is famous for its large xp reward in Attack and Strength, and for killing new HCIMs",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Waterfall Quest",
            "Holy Grail",
            "Dragon Slayer I",
            "Lost City"
        ],
        "answer": "Waterfall Quest"
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "This quest grants you free use of the Al Kharid Toll Gate",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Prince Ali Rescue",
            "Tourist Trap",
            "Goblin Diplomacy",
            "Pirate's Treasure"
        ],
        "answer": "Prince Ali Rescue"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "Which two dyes are required for Goblin Diplomacy?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Blue and Orange",
            "Blue and Purple",
            "Purple and Red",
            "Red and Blue"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue and Orange"
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "This quest serves as an introduction to the Herblore skill",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Druidic Ritual",
            "Witch's Potion",
            "Jungle Potion",
            "Nature Spirit"
        ],
        "answer": "Druidic Ritual"
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "Which of the following quests is NOT a free to play quest?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Vampyre Slayer",
            "Sheep Shearer",
            "The Restless Ghost",
            "Witch's House"
        ],
        "answer": "Witch's House"
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "Which of the following quests is NOT a members quest?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Gertrude's Cat",
            "Plague City",
            "Sea Slug",
            "The Restless Ghost"
        ],
        "answer": "The Restless Ghost"
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "This quest requires you to work with or be a part of the Black Arm Gang and Phoenix Gang",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Heroes' Quest",
            "Legends' Quest",
            "Dragon Slayer I",
            "Fight Arena"
        ],
        "answer": "Heroes' Quest"
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "The first of its kind this quest had a total of 10 parts, to celebrate being runescape's 100th quest",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Recipe for Disaster",
            "Dragon Slayer II",
            "Legends' Quest",
            "Monkey Madness II"
        ],
        "answer": "Recipe for Disaster"
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "This quest is a requirement to wield a Dragon Scimitar",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Monkey Madness",
            "Regicide",
            "Lost City",
            "Desert Treasure I"
        ],
        "answer": "Monkey Madness"
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "This quest rewards the player with the ability to use Ancient Magicks",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Desert Treasure I",
            "Tears of Guthix",
            "Mourning's End Part I",
            "Horror from the Deep"
        ],
        "answer": "Desert Treasure I"
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "This quest asks you to do simple task of obtaining Red Mahogany Logs",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "One Small Favour",
            "The Feud",
            "In Search of the Myreque",
            "Haunted Mine"
        ],
        "answer": "One Small Favour"
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "This quest is about the adventuring life of the Wise Old Man",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Swan Song",
            "Heroes' Quest",
            "One Small Favour",
            "Desert Treasure I"
        ],
        "answer": "Swan Song"
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "The seventh quest in the Elf Quest Series, it is known for its frustrating puzzle and frequently failed agility gap",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Mourning's End Part II",
            "The Song of the Elves",
            "Regicide",
            "The Underground Pass"
        ],
        "answer": "Mourning's End Part II"
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "The first quest to be 'backported' to Old School Runescape",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Land of the Goblins",
            "Tears of Guthix",
            "The Song of the Elves",
            "Swan Song"
        ],
        "answer": "Land of the Goblins"
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "This is the first ever Runescape quest",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Demon Slayer",
            "Cook's Assistant",
            "Romeo & Juliet",
            "Ernest the Chicken"
        ],
        "answer": "Cook's Assistant"
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "Known for its frustrating stealth section, this quest rewards you with the ability to name your wily or lazy cats",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Ratcatchers",
            "Gertrude's Cat",
            "Icthlarin's Little Helper",
            "The Giant Dwarf"
        ],
        "answer": "Ratcatchers"
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a boss in Recipe for Disaster?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Flambeed",
            "Karamel",
            "Dessourt",
            "Burnt Brulee"
        ],
        "answer": "Burnt Brulee"
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "This quest acts as an introduction to the Kingdom of Varlamore",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Children of the Sun",
            "A Kingdom Divided",
            "Secrets of the North",
            "Perilous Moons"
        ],
        "answer": "Children of the Sun"
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "After righteously assassinating the war hungry and violent frog named Cuthbert, he returns as the self-proclaimed",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Lord of Dread",
            "Lord of Death",
            "Son of Death",
            "Angel of Dread"
        ],
        "answer": "Lord of Dread"
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "In A Soul's Bane which of the following emotions is not represented?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Fear",
            "Rage",
            "Hopelessness",
            "Depression"
        ],
        "answer": "Depression"
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "Which of these potions do NOT act as a 'Saradomin Brew'",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Nectar",
            "Xeric's Aid",
            "Saradomin Brew",
            "Elder Potion"
        ],
        "answer": "Elder Potion"
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "As of April 9th 2024, this herb has the highest level requirement to clean",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Torstol",
            "Dwarf Weed",
            "Lantadyme",
            "Noxifer"
        ],
        "answer": "Torstol"
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "Which of these herbs has a level 40 herblore requirement to clean?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Irit leaf",
            "Toadflax",
            "Ranarr weed",
            "Torstol"
        ],
        "answer": "Irit leaf"
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "This tree requires level 90 woodcutting to chop",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Magics",
            "Yews",
            "Redwoods",
            "Artic Pine"
        ],
        "answer": "Redwoods"
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "Prior to the release of Sailing there are how many skills in OSRS?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "23",
            "24",
            "22",
            "21"
        ],
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "Which of the following Skills is NOT free to play?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Fishing",
            "Runecraft",
            "Crafting",
            "Fletching"
        ],
        "answer": "Fletching"
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "Which of the following Skills is NOT members only?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Agility",
            "Herblore",
            "Thieving",
            "Crafting"
        ],
        "answer": "Crafting"
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "This Rooftop course requires 90 agility",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Ardougne",
            "Rellekka",
            "Prifddinas",
            "Pollnivneach"
        ],
        "answer": "Ardougne"
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "The Ring of Endurance is an obtainable reward from this agility activity",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Hallowed Sepulchre",
            "Rooftop Agility Courses",
            "Prifddinas Agility Course",
            "Dorgesh-Kaan Agility Course"
        ],
        "answer": "Hallowed Sepulchre"
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "To create Divine super combat potions you need a herblore level of",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "90",
            "97",
            "94",
            "99"
        ],
        "answer": "97"
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": "To pickpocket elves you are required to have __ Thieving",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "85",
            "90",
            "75",
            "70"
        ],
        "answer": "85"
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "To create a Heavy Ballista you are required to have __ fletching level",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "72",
            "88",
            "84",
            "76"
        ],
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "Fletching Dragon Darts requires a fletching level of",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "95",
            "90",
            "99",
            "85"
        ],
        "answer": "95"
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": "The Alchemical Hydra requires a slayer level of __ to slay",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "95",
            "93",
            "92",
            "90"
        ],
        "answer": "95"
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": "Famous for dropping the Abyssal Whip, Abyssal demons require a slayer level of __ to slay",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "85",
            "87",
            "90",
            "92"
        ],
        "answer": "85"
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "Dust Devils require a slayer level of __ to slay",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "65",
            "70",
            "50",
            "55"
        ],
        "answer": "65"
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "To grow Dragonfruit trees you are required to have level __ Farming",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "81",
            "68",
            "57",
            "83"
        ],
        "answer": "81"
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "To grow Palm trees you are required to have level __ Farming",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "68",
            "66",
            "81",
            "57"
        ],
        "answer": "68"
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "The Chapel room requires level __ Construction",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "45",
            "50",
            "42",
            "44"
        ],
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "The Portal Nexus room requires level __ Construction",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "72",
            "80",
            "85",
            "75"
        ],
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "Master level Hunters' Rumours require a Hunter level of",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "91",
            "72",
            "57",
            "46"
        ],
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "Expert level Hunters' Rumours require a Hunter level of",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "91",
            "72",
            "57",
            "46"
        ],
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "To light Pyre Redwood logs you are required to have a Firemaking level of",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "95",
            "90",
            "92",
            "96"
        ],
        "answer": "95"
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "To light Magic logs you are required to have a Firemaking level of",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "75",
            "70",
            "85",
            "88"
        ],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "You are able to start cooking Sharks at level __ Cooking",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "80",
            "78",
            "76",
            "84"
        ],
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "You are able to start cooking Manta Rays at level __ Cooking",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "91",
            "93",
            "95",
            "97"
        ],
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "Individual Bones offered at the Chaos Altar or Gilded Altar with two burners lit give __ Prayer experience per bone",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "3.5x",
            "4x",
            "2x",
            "3x"
        ],
        "answer": "3.5x"
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "On average the Chaos Altar gives __ the amount of xp as a two burner Gilded Altar",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "2x",
            "1.5x",
            "1.9x",
            "1.7x"
        ],
        "answer": "2x"
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "In A Soul's Bane which of the following weapons is not used in the room representing Tolna's Anger?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Anger Sword",
            "Anger Spear",
            "Anger Mace",
            "Anger Warhammer"
        ],
        "answer": "Anger Warhammer"
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "In Dream Mentor you face multiple bosses representing Cyrisus's fear. Which of the following is NOT one of his fears?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "The Inadequacy",
            "The Everlasting",
            "The Illusive",
            "The Burden"
        ],
        "answer": "The Burden"
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "Which of the following spells is NOT in the Lunar Spellbook?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Monster Examine",
            "Barbarian Teleport",
            "Khazard Teleport",
            "Harmony Island Teleport"
        ],
        "answer": "Harmony Island Teleport"
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "Which of the following teleports is NOT in the Arceuus Spellbook?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Cemetery Teleport",
            "Barrows Teleport",
            "Ape Atoll Teleport",
            "Ice Plateau Teleport"
        ],
        "answer": "Ice Plateau Teleport"
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "Which of the following teleports is in the Lunar Spellbook?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Catherby Teleport",
            "Lassar Teleport",
            "Kharyrll Teleport",
            "Kourend Castle Teleport"
        ],
        "answer": "Catherby Teleport"
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "The spell Teleport to Target is available in every spellbook except for",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Standard",
            "Ancients",
            "Lunar",
            "Arceuus"
        ],
        "answer": "Arceuus"
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "The spell High Level Alchemy requires a Magic level of",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "55",
            "50",
            "45",
            "52"
        ],
        "answer": "55"
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "What is the highest level of Enchant spell?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Lvl-7 Enchant",
            "Lvl-8 Enchant",
            "Lvl-6 Enchant",
            "Lvl-9 Enchant"
        ],
        "answer": "Lvl-7 Enchant"
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT considered a curse spell?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Tele Block",
            "Snare",
            "Curse",
            "Charge"
        ],
        "answer": "Charge"
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "Home Teleport can refer to all except which spell?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Arceuus Home Teleport",
            "Teleport To House",
            "Lumbridge Home Teleport",
            "Moonclan Teleport"
        ],
        "answer": "Moonclan Teleport"
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "Tied with the Ghorrock Teleport, this spell has the highest level magic requirement at level 96",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Spellbook Swap",
            "Master Reanimation",
            "Sinister Offering",
            "Annakarl Teleport"
        ],
        "answer": "Spellbook Swap"
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "Order the Ancient Magick spells from weakest to strongest",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Rush, Burst, Blitz, Barrage",
            "Burst, Rush, Blitz, Barrage",
            "Blitz, Rush, Barrage, Burst",
            "Barrage, Blitz, Rush, Burst"
        ],
        "answer": "Rush, Burst, Blitz, Barrage"
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "Which of the following weapons can NOT autocast Ancient Magicks",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Ahrim's staff",
            "Nightmare Staff",
            "Blue Moon Spear",
            "Staff of the Dead"
        ],
        "answer": "Staff of the Dead"
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "Order these Ancient Magicks spells by level requirement from lowest to highest",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Smoke,Shadow,Blood,Ice",
            "Shadow,Smoke,Blood,Ice",
            "Smoke,Shadow,Ice,Blood",
            "Smoke,Blood,Shadow,Ice"
        ],
        "answer": "Smoke,Shadow,Blood,Ice"
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "Ice Barrage requires a magic level of __ to cast",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "96",
            "94",
            "92",
            "91"
        ],
        "answer": "94"
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "Which of the following teleports does NOT take you into the wilderness?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Ghorrock Teleport",
            "Annakarl Teleport",
            "Carrallanger Teleport",
            "Lassar Teleport"
        ],
        "answer": "Lassar Teleport"
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "Which of the following teleports would be considered dangerous?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Lassar Teleport",
            "Senntisten Teleport",
            "Paddewwa Teleport",
            "Dareeyak Teleport"
        ],
        "answer": "Dareeyak Teleport"
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of Ancient Magicks?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Blood",
            "Smoke",
            "Shadow",
            "Mist"
        ],
        "answer": "Mist"
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "Which of the following requires the Expert Reanimation spell?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Aviansie",
            "Abyssal Demon",
            "Horror",
            "Kalphite"
        ],
        "answer": "Kalphite"
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "Which of the following does NOT require the Master Reanimation spell?",
        "category": "Skilling",
        "options": [
            "Aviansie",
            "Abyssal Demon",
            "Dragon",
            "TzHaar"
        ],
        "answer": "TzHaar"
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "Which of the following is not considered a raid?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "The Chambers of Xeric",
            "Theatre Of Blood",
            "Tombs of Amascut",
            "Perilous Moons"
        ],
        "answer": "Perilous Moons"
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "Which of the following is a miniquest?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Daddy's Home",
            "Temple of the Eye",
            "Getting Ahead",
            "A Porcine of Interest"
        ],
        "answer": "Daddy's Home"
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a miniquest?",
        "category": "Quests",
        "options": [
            "Into the Tombs",
            "Lair of Tarn Razorlor",
            "Skippy and the Mogres",
            "Rag and Bone Man"
        ],
        "answer": "Rag and Bone Man"
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Hydra phase?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Sepentine",
            "Fire",
            "Extinguished",
            "Molten"
        ],
        "answer": "Molten"
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Dagannoth King?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Rex",
            "Prime",
            "Supreme",
            "Elite"
        ],
        "answer": "Elite"
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "Dagannoth Prime drops which of the following Rings?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Seers",
            "Warriors",
            "Archers",
            "Berserker"
        ],
        "answer": "Seers"
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "Dagannoth Supreme drops which of the following items?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Seercull",
            "Warriors Ring",
            "Berserker Ring",
            "Mud Battlestaff"
        ],
        "answer": "Seercull"
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "All of the following items are part of the Brimstone Ring except",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Hydra's Eye",
            "Hydra's Fang",
            "Hydra's Heart",
            "Hydra's Tail"
        ],
        "answer": "Hydra's Tail"
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "The Alchemical Speed-Runner GM Combat Achievement requires you to kill Hydra in",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "1 minute 20 seconds",
            "1 minute 30 seconds",
            "1 minute",
            "1 minute 50 seconds"
        ],
        "answer": "1 minute 20 seconds"
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "No Pressure refers to killing the Alchemical Hydra only using",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Dharok's Greataxe",
            "Your Fists",
            "Magic",
            "Ranged"
        ],
        "answer": "Dharok's Greataxe"
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "The Hydra's Claw has a drop rate of",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "1/1001",
            "1/100",
            "1/514",
            "1/513"
        ],
        "answer": "1/1001"
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "Vet'ion drops which of the following Voidwaker pieces?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Voidwaker blade",
            "Voidwaker hilt",
            "Voidwaker gem",
            "It doesn't"
        ],
        "answer": "Voidwaker blade"
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "Which of the following wilderness bosses drops the Ring of the Gods?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Vet'ion",
            "Venenatis",
            "Callisto",
            "Scorpia"
        ],
        "answer": "Vet'ion"
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "Of these wilderness bosses, pick the odd one out.",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Venenatis",
            "Spindel",
            "Artio",
            "Calvar'ion"
        ],
        "answer": "Venenatis"
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "Of these wilderness bosses, pick the odd one out",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Calvar'ion",
            "Venenatis",
            "Vet'ion",
            "Callisto"
        ],
        "answer": "Calvar'ion"
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "Which of the following does not drop a Dragon pickaxe?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Chaos Elemental",
            "Kalphite Queen",
            "King Black Dragon",
            "Giant Mole"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Mole"
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a phase of the Great Olm?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Acid",
            "Flame",
            "Crystal",
            "Blood"
        ],
        "answer": "Blood"
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "To protect against a Red Sphere of Aggression from Olm you would",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Protect From Melee",
            "Protect From Magic",
            "Protect From Missiles",
            "Stand under another player"
        ],
        "answer": "Protect From Melee"
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an Olm special attack?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Crystal Burst",
            "Lightning",
            "Swap",
            "Falling Crystals"
        ],
        "answer": "Falling Crystals"
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "Which of the following is considered a phase-unique attack from Olm?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Crystal Burst",
            "Lightning",
            "Sphere of Aggression",
            "Fire Wall"
        ],
        "answer": "Fire Wall"
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "What is the first of Olm's special attacks?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Crystal Burst",
            "Lightning",
            "Swap",
            "Autoheal"
        ],
        "answer": "Crystal Burst"
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "Olm's Head is weak to",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Range",
            "Magic",
            "Melee",
            "All of the Above"
        ],
        "answer": "Range"
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "Olm's Right claw is weak to",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Magic",
            "Ranged",
            "Crush",
            "Stab"
        ],
        "answer": "Magic"
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "Olm's Left claw is weak to",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Range",
            "Magic",
            "Melee",
            "All of the Above"
        ],
        "answer": "Melee"
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "Which of the following bosses is found in the Theatre of Blood?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Sotetseg",
            "Muttadile",
            "Tekton",
            "Kephri"
        ],
        "answer": "Sotetseg"
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "Which of the following bosses is NOT found in the Theatre of Blood?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Xarpus",
            "Pestilent Bloat",
            "The Maiden of Sugadinti",
            "Vasa Nistirio"
        ],
        "answer": "Vasa Nistirio"
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "Which of these Theatre of Blood bosses is first?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Boss order is random",
            "Boss order is up the player's choice",
            "Nylocas Vasilias",
            "The Maiden of Sugadinti"
        ],
        "answer": "The Maiden of Sugadinti"
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "question": "Which of these Chambers of Xeric Bosses come first?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Boss order is random",
            "Boss order is up the player's choice",
            "Lizardman Shamans",
            "Muttadiles"
        ],
        "answer": "Boss order is random"
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "Which of these Challenge Mode Chambers of Xeric Bosses come first?",
        "category": "PvM",
        "options": [
            "Tekton",
            "Vasa Nistirio",
            "Lizardman Shamans",
            "Muttadiles"
        ],
        "answer": "Tekton"
    }
]